https://www.aaceinc.org/privacy-policy/

AACEINC.org (“American Association of Cat Enthusiasts”) operates AACEINC.org and may operate other websites. It is American Association of Cat Enthusiasts’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites. Website Visitors Like most website operators, American Association of Cat Enthusiasts collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. American Association of Cat Enthusiasts purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how American Association of Cat Enthusiasts visitors use its website. From time to time, American Association of Cat Enthusiasts may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. American Association of Cat Enthusiasts also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on AACEINC.org blogs/sites. American Association of Cat Enthusiasts only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left. Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information Certain visitors to American Association of Cat Enthusiasts websites choose to interact with American Association of Cat Enthusiasts in ways that require American Association of Cat Enthusiasts to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that American Association of Cat Enthusiasts gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at AACEINC.org to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with American Association of Cat Enthusiasts are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, American Association of Cat Enthusiasts collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with American Association of Cat Enthusiasts. American Association of Cat Enthusiasts does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. Aggregated Statistics American Association of Cat Enthusiasts may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. American Association of Cat Enthusiasts may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, American Association of Cat Enthusiasts does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information American Association of Cat Enthusiasts discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on American Association of Cat Enthusiasts behalf or to provide services available at American Association of Cat Enthusiasts websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using American Association of Cat Enthusiasts websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. American Association of Cat Enthusiasts will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, American Association of Cat Enthusiasts discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when American Association of Cat Enthusiasts believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of American Association of Cat Enthusiasts, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an American Association of Cat Enthusiasts website and have supplied your email address, American Association of Cat Enthusiasts may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with American Association of Cat Enthusiasts and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. American Association of Cat Enthusiasts takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. Cookies A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. American Association of Cat Enthusiasts uses cookies to help American Association of Cat Enthusiasts identify and track visitors, their usage of American Association of Cat Enthusiasts website, and their website access preferences. American Association of Cat Enthusiasts visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using American Association of Cat Enthusiasts websites, with the drawback that certain features of American Association of Cat Enthusiasts websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. Business Transfers If American Association of Cat Enthusiasts, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that American Association of Cat Enthusiasts goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of American Association of Cat Enthusiasts may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. Ads Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by American Association of Cat Enthusiasts and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. Privacy Policy Changes Although most changes are likely to be minor, American Association of Cat Enthusiasts may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in American Association of Cat Enthusiasts sole discretion. American Association of Cat Enthusiasts encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a AACEINC.org account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Popular Posts
Acne No More Review
8 Week Custom Keto Diet Plan Review
Trimifi Diet System Review
Adaptive Body Boost Review
Old School New Body Review
